A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of David Bell FA624
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Trustee Meeting Files, 1966 - 1980; III
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 10, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 591)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 25-26, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 592)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 23, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 593)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 2, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 594)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 24-25, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 595)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 22, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 596)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 10-11, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 597)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 11, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 598)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 23-24, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 599)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 22, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 600)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 29-31, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 601)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 29, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 602)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 29-30, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 603)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 28, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 604)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 28-29, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 605)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 27, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 606)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 8-9, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 607)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 7, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 608)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 7, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 609)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 29-30, 1974, 1973 - 1974 (Box 22, Folder 610)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 28, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 611)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 28-29, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 612)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 27, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 613)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 25-26, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 614)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 24, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 615)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 14-15, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 616)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 13, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 617)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 6, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 618)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 28-29, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 619)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 27, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 620)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 27-28, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 621)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 26, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 622)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 25, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 26, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 624)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 12-14, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 25, 1975, 1974 - 1975 (Box 23, Folder 626)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 26-27, 1975, 1974 - 1975 (Box 23, Folder 627)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 25, 1975, 1974 - 1975 (Box 23, Folder 628)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, May 22, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 629)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 26-27, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 630)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 25, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 631)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 25-26, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 632)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 24, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 633)
  - Appropriation Request, FY 1975, 1974 - 1975 (Box 23, Folder 634)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, Sept. 24, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 635)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 12-13, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 636)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 11, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 637)
  - Joint International/R&E Committee Meetings, Mar. 24, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 638)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 25-26, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 639)
  - Special Board Review Meetings, June - July 1976, 1975 - 1976 (Box 23, Folder 640)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 23, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 641)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 23- 24, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 642)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 22, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 643)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 1976 - Education Paper (Box 23, Folder 644)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 9-10, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 645)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 16, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 646)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 24-25, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 647)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, May 23, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 648)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 23-24, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 649)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 22, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 650)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 29-30, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 651)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 8-9, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 652)
  - Joint International/R&E Committee Meetings, Dec. 7, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 653)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 30-31, 1978, 1977 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 654)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 29, 1978, 1977 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 655)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 29-30, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 656)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, India - Oct. 2-6, 1978, 1977 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 657)
  - Trustee Activities in India, Oct. 1978, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 658)
  - Trustee Activities in India, 1978 January - May (Box 24, Folder 659)
  - Trustee Activities in India, 1978 June - November (Box 24, Folder 660)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 6-8, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 661)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 29-30, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 29-30, 1979 - background material, 1978 - 1979 (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 28, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 664)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 28-29, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 665)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 27, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 666)
  - Communications Committee Meeting, June 1979 (Box 24, Folder 667)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 26-27, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 668)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 27, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 669)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 13-14, 1979, 1979 - 1980 (Box 25, Folder 670)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 12, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 671)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 21, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 672)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 27-28, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 673)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 27-28, 1980 - background material (Box 25, Folder 674)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 26, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 675)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 26-27, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 676)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 25-26, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 677)
  - International Comnittee Meeting, Sept. 24, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 678)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 11-12, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 679)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 10, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 680)
- Agriculture Files, 1966 - 1979; IV
  Series IV, Agriculture Files (1966-1979), contains material on the administrative and program development of five international centers for agricultural research and development. It includes extensive material on the meetings of the Consultative Group for International Research (CGIAR), and its Task Force on International Assistance for National Agricultural Research (ISNAR), of the annual International Centers Week, and of the International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI).
  This series is divided into the following four sub-series:
  A. International Agricultural Center Files (2.5 boxes)
  B. CGIAR/ISNAR Files (2 boxes)
  C. Agriculture Meeting and Conference Files (1.5 boxes)
  D. International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI) Files (1 box)
  - International Agricultural Center Files, 1966 - 1980; A
    The first section of this subseries consists of general material on the administration and program development of five international agricultural centers. The second section of this subseries consists of files on each agricultural center.
    This sub-series is further divided into two sections. The first section is arranged chronologically. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    The second section is arranged alphabetically by Ford Foundation program area in effect at that time (A&P, LAC, MEA) and chronologically within each area. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Agriculture - General, 1967 - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 681)
    - Agriculture - General, 1971 - 1973 (Box 26, Folder 682)
    - Agriculture - General, 1974 - 1980 (Box 26, Folder 683)
    - International Agricultural Centers - General, 1966 - 1967 (Box 26, Folder 684)
    - International Agricultural Centers - General, 1968 - 1969 (Box 26, Folder 685)
    - International Agricultural Centers - General, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 686)
    - International Agricultural Centers - General, 1971 - 1980 (Box 26, Folder 687)
    - International Agricultural Centers Discussion, the Hague, Dec. 1969, 1969 - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 688)
    - A&P - Intensive Agricultural District Program (IADP) - India, 1966 - 1967 (Box 26, Folder 689)
    - A&P - Indian Fertilizer Program, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 690)
    - A&P - Ford Foundation Indian Agricultural Consultants Meeting - Jan. 26-27,1968, 1967 - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 691)
    - A&P - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 1970 - 1976 (Box 26, Folder 692)
    - A&P - Meeting re: ICRISAT, Jan. 20, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 693)
    - A&P - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI), 1966 - 1969 (Box 27, Folder 694)
    - A&P - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI), 1970 - 1978 (Box 27, Folder 695)
    - A&P - IRRI Outlook Study, 1968 - 1969 (Box 27, Folder 696)
    - A&P - IRRI Conference, Los Banos, Sept. 30 - Oct. 3, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 697)
    - LAC - Latin America - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT), 1966 - 1973 (Box 27, Folder 698)
    - LAC - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT), 1966 - 1971 (Box 27, Folder 699)
    - LAC - Agriculture - Latin America, 1966 - 1970 (Box 27, Folder 700)
    - MEA - Arid Lands Development Program (ALAD), 1966 - 1976 (Box 27, Folder 701)
    - MEA - ALAD Conference, Beirut, April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 702)
    - MEA - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA), Rome - February 10-12, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 703)
    - MEA - ICARDA Subcommittee of CGIAR - Washington, Oct. 29-31, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 704)
    - MEA - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 1966 - 1968 (Box 27, Folder 705)
    - MEA - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 706)
    - MEA - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 1970 - 1977 (Box 27, Folder 707)
    - MEA - Middle East Center - CGIAR Subcommittee Meeting, London, Oct. 1-21, 1971, 1973 - 1974 (Box 28, Folder 708)
    - MEA - Agriculture - Other Middle East, 1967 - 1970 (Box 28, Folder 709)
    - Proposed International Water Management Institute, 1969 - 1970 (Box 28, Folder 710)
    - Other Proposed International Centers, 1969 - 1977 (Box 28, Folder 711)
  - CGIAR/ISNAR Files, 1971 - 1979; B
    The first section of this subseries consists of material on the organization of the Consultative Group for International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) and the procedures of its committee meetings. The second section of this subseries consists of material on the formation and committee meetings of the CGIAR's Task Force on International Assistance for National Agricultural Research (ISNAR).
    This sub-series is further divided into two sections. Within each section, the folders are arranged chronologically. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research - General, 1971 - 1973 (Box 28, Folder 712)
    - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research - General, 1974 - 1979 (Box 28, Folder 713)
    - IBRD Consultative Group Meetings, Jan. 14-15, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 714)
    - IBRD Consultative Group Meetings, May 19, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 715)
    - IBRD Consultative Group Meetings, Dec. 3, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 716)
    - IBRD Consultative Group Meetings, Nov. 1-3, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 717)
    - CGIAR - Subcommittee on Center Review Procedures, 1973 - 1974 (Box 28, Folder 718)
    - CGIAR Meeting, Oct. 30-31, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 719)
    - CGIAR Review Committee, Mar. 18, 1976, 1975 - 1976 (Box 28, Folder 720)
    - CGIAR Review Committee, July 22-23, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 721)
    - CGIAR Review Committee, Sept. 14-15, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 722)
    - CGIAR Meeting, Oct. 27-29, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 723)
    - CGIAR Task Force on International Assistance for National Agricultural Research, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 724)
    - CGIAR Task Force on International Assistance for National Agricultural Research, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 725)
    - CGIAR/ISNAR Task Force - Nairobi, June 1978 (Box 29, Folder 726)
    - ISNAR Committee Meeting - Geneva, Feb. 15- 16, 1979, 1978 - 1979 (Box 29, Folder 727)
    - ISNAR and CG Meetings - Paris, May 2-4, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 728)
    - CGIAR-ISNAR Committee Meetings, Oct. 26, 1979, 1978 - 1979 (Box 29, Folder 729)
  - Agriculture Meeting and Conference Files, 1969 - 1980; C
    The first section of this subseries consists of material on the annual meetings of International Centers Week. The second section of this subseries consists of material on Ford and Rockefeller Foundation Conferences on Agriculture and Development.
    - International Centers Week - Sept. 28 - Oct. 2, 1970, 1969 - 1970 (Box 29, Folder 730)
    - International Centers Week - Oct. 5-8, 1971, 1970 - 1971 (Box 29, Folder 731)
    - International Centers Week - July 31 - Aug. 4, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 732)
    - International Centers Week - Aug. 1973 (Box 29, Folder 733)
    - International Centers Week - 1974, 1974 - 1975 (Box 29, Folder 734)
    - International Centers Week - 1975 (Box 30, Folder 735)
    - International Centers Week, July 28-30, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 736)
    - International Centers Week, Sept. 1977 (Box 30, Folder 737)
    - International Centers Week, Nov. 6-10, 1978, 1978 - 1979 (Box 30, Folder 738)
    - International Centers Week, Oct. 29 - Nov. 2, 1979, 1979 - 1980 (Box 30, Folder 739)
    - FF/RF Meetings re: Agricultural Institutes, Mar. 10-14, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 740)
    - Bellagio Conference on Agricultural Development, April 23-25, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 741)
    - International Agricultural Institutes Meetings, Oct. 27-31, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 742)
    - Post-Bellagio Agricultural Group, 1968, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 743)
    - Bellagio Conference on Agriculture, April 9-10, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 744)
    - Bellagio Agricultural Group, Dec. 3-4, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 745)
    - World Food Outlook, Possible Institute - UN Conferences, 1973 - 1974, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 746)
    - Meeting on Social Science Research and Rural Development, April 29-30, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 747)
  - International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI) Files, 1974 - 1979; D
    This sub-series consists of material on the organization, administration, and periodic meetings of the International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI).
    This sub-series is arranged in chronological order. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - International Food Policy Research Institute - Ottawa, Sept. 1974 (Box 31, Folder 748)
    - International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI) - General, 1974 - 1979 (Box 31, Folder 749)
    - IFPRI - Washington, Jan. 1975 (Box 31, Folder 750)
    - IFPRI - Washington, May 1975 (Box 31, Folder 751)
    - IFPRI - Board of Trustees Meeting, July 1975 (Box 31, Folder 752)
    - IFPRI - Board of Trustees Meeting, July 1975 - Summary (Box 31, Folder 753)
    - IFPRI Executive Committee, Dec. 1975 (Box 31, Folder 754)
    - IFPRI Trustees Meeting, Feb. 1976 (Box 31, Folder 755)
    - IFPRI Executive Committee, July 1976 (Box 31, Folder 756)
    - IFPRI Board Meeting, Sept. 1976 (Box 31, Folder 757)
    - IFPRI Executive Committee, Oct. 1976 (Box 31, Folder 758)
    - IFPRI Board Meeting, Feb. 1977, 1976 - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 759)
    - IFPRI Search Committee, June 1977, 1976 - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 760)
    - IFPRI Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 1977 (Box 31, Folder 761)
    - IFPRI Board of Trustees Meeting, Feb. 1978 (Box 31, Folder 762)
    - IFPRI Executive Commi ttee, May 1978 (Box 31, Folder 763)
    - IFPRI, Ottawa, Aug. 1978 (Box 31, Folder 764)
    - IFPRI Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 1978 (Box 31, Folder 765)
    - IFPRI Board Meeting, Rome, Feb. 1979, 1978 - 1979 (Box 31, Folder 766)
    - IFPRI - Kate Hathaway, 1978 - 1979 (Box 31, Folder 767)
    - IFPRI Meeting - Mar. 1979 (Box 31, Folder 768)
    - IFPRI Board of Trustees, June 1979 (Box 31, Folder 769)
    - IFPRI Board of Trustees, Sept. 1979 (Box 31, Folder 770)
- Population Files, 1966 - 1981; V
  Series V, Population Files (1966-1981), contains material on the program planning, evaluation, and administration of the Population Program. It includes extensive material on some principal grantee organizations and on Ford and Rockefeller (Bellagio) Conferences on Population and Development.
  A. Ford Foundation Population Program Files (2 boxes)
  B. Meetings and Conferences (1 box)
  - Ford Foundation Population Program Files, A
    The first section of this subseries consists of material on the program planning, administration, and evaluation of the Population Program. The second section of this subseries consists of files on grantee organizations.
    This subseries is further divided into two sections. The first section is arranged chronologically. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order. The second section is arranged alphabetically. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Ford Foundation Population Program, 1966 - 1969 (Box 32, Folder 771)
    - Ford Foundation Population Program, 1970 - 1976 (Box 32, Folder 772)
    - Ford Foundation Population Program, 1977 - 1980 (Box 32, Folder 773)
    - Population - General, 1975 - 1979 (Box 32, Folder 774)
    - Greep Review and Follow-up, 1976 - 1977 (Box 32, Folder 775)
    - Califano Meeting (21 June 1977) (Box 32, Folder 776)
    - Health, Nutrition, and Population (HNP), 1978 - 1981 (Box 32, Folder 777)
    - Population Information Paper (Dec. 1979) (Box 32, Folder 778)
    - Institute for Human Reproduction, 1966 - 1970 (Box 33, Folder 779)
    - International Centre for Diarrhoeal Disease Research, Bangladesh (ICDDRB), 1976 - 1980 (Box 33, Folder 780)
    - ICDDRB Meeting - Geneva (Feb. 1979), 1978 - 1979 (Box 33, Folder 781)
    - International Population Research Institute, 1970 - 1971 (Box 33, Folder 782)
    - The Population Council, 1966 - 1977 (Box 33, Folder 783)
    - The Population Council, 1978 - 1981 (Box 33, Folder 784)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities, 1967 - 1975 (Box 33, Folder 785)
    - World Health Organization (WHO) Expanded Program, 1971 - 1979 (Box 33, Folder 786)
  - Meetings and Conferences, 1968 - 1980; B
    The first section of this subseries consists of material on Population Conferences funded by the Ford Foundation. The second section of this subseries consists of material on the Bellagio Population Conferences funded by the Rockefeller Foundation, attended by Mr. Bell and to which he contributed papers.
    This subseries is further divided into two sections. Within each section, the folders are arranged chronologically. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Ford Foundation Population Meeting, Lake Como, Italy, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 787)
    - Ford Foundation Population Meeting, Elsinore, Denmark, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 788)
    - Ford Foundation Population Meeting, Cali, Colombia, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 789)
    - Ford Foundation Conference - Social Science Research on Population and Development, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 790)
    - Meeting on Public Sector Involvement in Reproductive Sciences, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 791)
    - Ford Foundation Population Meeting, Bangkok, Thailand, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 792)
    - Bellagio I Population Conference, 1969 - 1970 (Box 34, Folder 793)
    - Bellagio Population Group - Interim Committee, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 794)
    - Bellagio II Population Conference, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 795)
    - Bellagio III Population Conference, 1970 - 1976 (Box 34, Folder 796)
    - Possible Bellagio IV Population Meeting, 1975 - 1976 (Box 34, Folder 797)
    - Bellagio IV Population Conference, 1976 - 1977 (Box 34, Folder 798)
    - Bellagio Conference: Health and Population in Developing Countries, 1977 - 1978 (Box 34, Folder 799)
    - Bellagio Conference: Health and Population in Developing Countries, 1978 - 1980 (Box 34, Folder 800)
    - Bellagio Meeting on Development Research, 1973 - 1976 (Box 34, Folder 801)
- Subject Files, 1966-1981; VI
  Series VI, Subject Files (1966-1981), contains material on selected Foundation procedures, divisions and offices of the Foundation other than the Office of the Vice President/International Division, selected subject areas in which grants were made, selected surveys and studies.
  This series consists of material on selected subject areas in which grants were made, divisions of the Foundation other than the OVP/ID, internal Foundation procedures, selected surveys and studies. It is arranged alphabetically. Within each file, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - CIA Orphans - CIA Orphans and All That, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 802)
  - CIA Orphans - Representatives' Responses, Sutton Memo 3/15/67, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 803)
  - CIA Orphans - Rusk Committee, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 804)
  - Cleaveland Grants - National Affairs, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 805)
  - Cultural Grants, 1967 - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 806)
  - Environmental Grants, 1971 - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 807)
  - Evaluation of Grants, 1966 - 1979 (Box 35, Folder 808)
  - Foundations (Other), 1967 - 1981 (Box 35, Folder 809)
  - Human Rights - Human Rights and Intellectual Freedom, 1975 - 1981 (Box 36, Folder 810)
  - Human Rights - Indochinese Refugees, 1979 - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 811)
  - Human Rights - Migration and Refugees, 1979 - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 812)
  - Human Rights - Princeton Seminar on Human Rights, Foreign Policy and the Media, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 813)
  - International Economic Order - Planning Agenda, 1972 - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 814)
  - International Economic Order - Working Group, 1977 - 1978 (Box 36, Folder 815)
  - Language and Linguistics Survey, 1966 - 1968 (Box 36, Folder 816)
  - Libraries, 1971 - 1975 (Box 36, Folder 817)
  - National Affairs Division, 1967 - 1977 (Box 36, Folder 818)
  - Office of the Secretary, 1966 - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 819)
  - Outside Affiliation and Remuneration, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 820)
  - "Pay As You Earn", 1970 - 1971 (Box 36, Folder 821)
  - Task Force - FAPs, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 822)
  - Task Force - FAPs, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 823)
  - Task Force - FAPs, 1972 - 1973 (Box 37, Folder 824)
  - Task Force - Financial Reporting and Accounting, 1971 - 1973 (Box 37, Folder 825)
  - Task Force - Foundation Procedures, 1972 - 1974 (Box 37, Folder 826)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1969 - Foundation Executives' Meeting (Box 37, Folder 827)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1969 - ID Follow-up, 1969 - 1970 (Box 37, Folder 828)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1969 - ID Follow-up, 1971 - 1972 (Box 37, Folder 829)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1969 - ID Follow-up, 1973 - 1974 (Box 37, Folder 830)
  - Urbanization Study, 1970 - 1971 (Box 37, Folder 831)
- Appendix A: Reports Accessioned
  The following reports were removed from this collection. The number at the left is the assigned accession number. The list is alphabetical by title.
  - Bresnan, John. Actions concerning China in FY 1980, 1980 September (Report 7037)